Association for Research and Enlightenment Collection
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
Association for Research and Enlightenment Collection
1931 2020
Coll. 14
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
100 Linear Feet
The Association for Research and Enlightenment (1931-present)
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of administrative records, publications, research data, and audio-visual materials that document the development and activities of the Association for Research and Enlightenment in Virginia Beach, Virginia.
Arrangement
Arranged in 8 series: 1. A.R.E. Clinic. 2. Management files, 1931-2019. 3. Prayer Services. 4. Publications, 1931-2019. 5. Regional activities. 6. Research. 7. Study Groups, 1932-2011. 8. Audiovisual materials.
Boxes 1- 42; Publications
Box 1: A.R.E. Bulletin, 1932-1945 Box 2: A.R.E. Bulletin, 1945-1965 Box 3: articles, 1949-1978 Box 4: The Searchlight, 1946-1955 Box 4A: The Searchlight, 1956-1965 Box 4B: Diary-Letters, 1945-1948; Newsletter from the Office, 1948; Association News, 1948-1949; News from Headquarters, 1949-1953 Box 5: News from Headquarters, 1954-1958; A.R.E. News, 1966-1972 Box 6: A.R.E. News, 1973-1984 Box 7: A.R.E. Journal, 1966-1973 Box 8: A.R.E. Journal, 1974-1980 Box 9: A.R.E. Journal, 1980-1984 Box 10: announcements, articles, Congress publications, membership letters, 1932-1938 Box 11: announcements, articles, Congress publications, membership letters, 1938-1943 Box 12: announcements, articles, Congress publications, membership letters, 1943-1945 Box 13: announcements, articles, Congress publications, membership letters, 1945-1950 Box 13A: announcements, articles, conference publications, Congress publications, membership letters, 1950-1952 Box 14: announcements, articles, conference publications, Congress publications, membership letters, 1953-1955 Box 15: announcements, articles, conference publications, Congress publications, membership letters, 1955-1957 Box 16: announcements, articles, conference publications, Congress publications, membership letters, 1958-1962 Box 17: announcements, articles, conference publications, Congress publications, membership letters, 1963-1966 Box 18: announcements, articles, conference publications, Congress publications, membership letters, 1967-1969 Box 19: announcements, articles, conference publications, Congress publications, membership letters, 1970-1977 Box 20: conference publications; membership letters, 1978-1981 Box 21: conference publications; membership letters, 1982-1983 Box 22: conference publications; membership letters, 1983-1985 Box 23: conference publications; membership letters, 1986-1987 Box 24: conference publications; membership letters, 1988-1989 Box 25: conference publications; membership letters, 1990-1991 Box 26: conference publications; membership letters, 1992-1994 Box 27: conference publications; membership letters, 1995-1997 Box 28: conference publications; membership letters, 1998-2001 Box 29: conference publications; membership letters, 2003-2012
Box 30: Weekly Readings Extracts, 1944-1945 Box 31: Weekly Readings Extracts, 1946-1948 Box 32: newsletters: Ancient Mysteries; Commentary; Covenant; Earth Changes Update; Face to Face; Personal Spirituality; Perspective, 1980-2009 Box 33: newsletters and and magazines: The Psychic Observer; Reflections; Selections from the Edgar Cayce Readings; True Health; Venture Inward newsletter; Venture Inward, 1948-2015
Box 34: A.R.E. Congress, 1932-1977 Box 35: A.R.E. Congress, 1978-1985 Box 36: A.R.E. Congress, 1986-1990 Box 37: A.R.E. Congress, 1991-2000
Box 38: All God's Children: A Publication for Educators and Parents, 1982-1991; A.R.E. Camp, 1960-2007; A.R.E. Children's Magazine, 1969-1970; A.R.E. Treasure Trove, 1971-1972 Box 38A: A.R.E. Treasure Trove, 1973-1975; A.R.E. Youth Activities, 1962-1996; Co-optopus coloring book, 1978-1995; Green Woods School News, 1982; Kundalini for Youth, 1970-1985 Box 39: Kundalini for Youth, 1970-1985; The New Millennium, 1996-2000
Box 40: Edgar Cayce Publishing Company, 1945-1961 Box 41: Edgar Cayce Publishing Company, 1934-1962 Box 42: Edgar Cayce Publishing Company, 1945-1967
Boxes 43-55; Study Groups
Box 43: publications, 1969-2011 Box 44: correspondence, 1932-2000 Box 45: course materials and manuscripts, 1952-2004 Box 46: minutes, 1932-1976 Box 47: minutes, 1934-1940; newsletters: A Search for God Study Groups, Chrysalis Rising, Group Guidelines, 1961-2000; Parallel Bible Material, 1979 Box 48: publications, 1932-1996 Box 49: research notes, 1950-1956; workbooks, 1934-2002 Box 50: workbooks, 1980-2000 Box 51: Bible Study materials, 1939-1958 Box 52: Bible Study materials, 1941-1969 Box 53: Bible Study materials, 1962-1968 Box 54: Bible Study materials, 1958-1968 Box 55: Bible Study materials, 1932-1968
Related Materials
A.R.E. Press books located in Special Collections section of E.C.F. Archival Storage.
- Board of Trustees, 1931 2020
  - Minutes and Correspondence, 1932 2020
    - Box 56
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1931 1932; Folder 56:1
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1932 1937; Folder 56:2
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1937 1945; Folder 56:3
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1945; Folder 56:4
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1946 1947; Folder 56:5
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1947 1948; Folder 56:6
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1949 1950; Folder 56:7
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1951 1952; Folder 56:8
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1953 1955; Folder 56:9
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1956 1958; Folder 56:10
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1959 1962; Folder 56:11
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1963 1964; Folder 56:12
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1965 1967; Folder 56:13
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1968 1971; Folder 56:14
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1972 1973; Folder 56:15
    - Box 57
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1971 1979; Folder 57:1
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1980 1983; Folder 57:2
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1984; Folder 57:3
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1985; Folder 57:4
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1986; Folder 57:5
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1987; Folder 57:6
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1988 1989; Folder 57:7
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1990; Folder 57:8-57:11
    - Box 58
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1991; Folder 58:1-58:2
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1992; Folder 58:3-58:6
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1993; Folder 58:7-58:9
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1994; Folder 58:10-58:11
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1995; Folder 58:12
    - Box 59
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1995; Folder 59:1-59:2
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1996; Folder 59:3
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1997; Folder 59:4
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1998; Folder 59:5
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 1999; Folder 59:6-59:7
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2000; Folder 59:8-59:9
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2001; Folder 59:10-59:12
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2002; Folder 59:13-59:14
    - Box 60
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2003; Folder 60:1-60:2
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2004; Folder 60:3-60:5
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2005; Folder 60:6-60:8
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2006; Folder 60:9
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2007; Folder 60:10-60:12
    - Box 61
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2007; Folder 61:1
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2008; Folder 61:2
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2009 2010; Folder 61:3
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2011; Folder 61:4
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2012; Folder 61:5
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2013; Folder 61:6
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2014; Folder 61:7
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2015; Folder 61:8
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2016; Folder 61:9
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2017; Folder 61:10
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2018; Folder 61:11-61:12
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2019; Folder 61:13
    - Box 62
      - A.R.E. Board of Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2020; Folder 62:1
  - Supplements, 1956 2010
    - Box 63
      - Arctic Crescent A.R.E. headquarters mortgage, 1956 1964; Folder 63:1
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1956 1958; Folder 63:2
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1959; Folder 63:3
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1960 1964; Folder 63:4
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1965; Folder 63:5
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1966 1967; Folder 63:6
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1968 1969; Folder 63:7
      - A.R.E. board supplements; National Inventors Council application, 1957; Folder 63:8
      - A.R.E. board supplements; Highlights from the Edgar Cayce Work Readings compiled by Robert Adriance, 1968; Folder 63:9
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1970; Folder 63:10
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1971; Folder 63:11
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1972; Folder 63:12
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1973; Folder 63:13-63:14
    - Box 64
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1974; Folder 64:1-64:2
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1975; Folder 64:3-64:5
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1977; Folder 64:6-64:8
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1978; Folder 64:9-64:10
    - Box 65
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1978; Folder 65:1
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1979; Folder 65:2-65:3
      - A.R.E. staff minutes / bulletins, 1979; Folder 65:4
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1980; Folder 65:5-65:8
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1981; Folder 65:9-65:10
    - Box 66
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1982; Folder 66:1-66:2
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1983; Folder 66:3-66:6
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1984; Folder 66:7-66:11
    - Box 67
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1985; Folder 67:1-67:3
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1986; Folder 67:4-67:6
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1987 1988; Folder 67:7
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1988; Folder 67:8
    - Box 68
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1989; Folder 68:1-68:2
      - A.R.E. board supplements, 1990 1995; Folder 68:3
      - book [Robert's Rules of Order], 1990; Folder 68:4
      - board committee minutes, 1992; Folder 68:5
      - A.R.E. Congress Executive Team Handbook, 1993 1995; Folder 68:6-68:7
      - A.R.E. organizational survey, 1997; Folder 68:8
      - The 2020 Vision Long Range Master Plan, 1997; Folder 68:9
      - Board of Trustees manual, 2006; Folder 68:10
      - Board of Trustees Blue Book, 2010; Folder 68:11
    - Box 69, Board of Trustees bound minutes 1971-1982; 1985; 1986
- Management, 1931 2004
  - Box 70
    - articles of incorporation, 1931; Folder 70:1
    - correspondence [Carl Jung to Lily M. Buser], 1951; Folder 70:2
    - federal and state tax documentation, 1932 1980; Folder 70:3
    - payroll data, 1944 1945; Folder 70:4
    - visitor register [A.R.E. offices], 1944 1956; Folder 70:5
    - visitor register [A.R.E. Annual Congress], 1956 1958; Folder 70:6
    - visitor register [A.R.E. headquarters], 1962 1963; Folder 70:7
    - visitor register [A.R.E. headquarters], 1963 1965; Folder 70:8
    - visitor register [A.R.E. headquarters], 1966 1967; Folder 70:9
    - visitor register [A.R.E. headquarters], 1967 1968; Folder 70:10
    - visitor register [A.R.E. headquarters], 1971; Folder 70:11
    - visitor register [A.R.E. headquarters], 2006 2008; Folder 70:12
    - visitor register [A.R.E. headquarters], 2010 2011; Folder 70:13
    - correspondence [Petroleum International], 1959 1960; Folder 70:14
    - management records, 1969; Folder 70:15
    - correspondence [A.R.E. Library and Conference Center construction], 1972 1975; Folder 70:16
    - correspondence [A.R.E. Library and Conference Center dedication], 1974 1975; Folder 70:17-70:18
    - correspondence [A.R.E. Library and Conference Center fundraising], 1973 1974; Folder 70:19
    - departmental staff meeting minutes, 1969 1971; Folder 70:20
    - departmental staff meeting minutes, 1973; Folder 70:21
  - Box 71
    - ledger, 1939 1947; Item 71:1
      Related Materials
      Item 71:2, ledger, 1943-1946 located in oversize.
  - Box 72
    - departmental staff meeting minutes, 1974; Folder 72:1
    - management study [John H. Witmer and Company], 1975; Folder 72:2
    - management records; staff minutes, 1977 1978; Folder 72:3
    - correspondence [Fredrica Fields] stained glass installation in A.R.E. meditation room, 1977 1978; Folder 72:4
    - photographs [Fredrica Fields stained glass installation in A.R.E. meditation room], 1978; Folder 72:5-72:6
    - correspondence [Miriam Sommerburg] sculpture donation, 1979 1980; Folder 72:7
    - correspondence [Geoffrey Sykes], 1974; Folder 72:8
    - financial statements [Marshalls Hotel Corporation], 1975; Folder 72:9
    - correspondence [Thomas C. King] San Saba, Texas oil drilling, 1980 1982; Folder 72:10
    - staff minutes, 1980; Folder 72:11
    - management records, 1981-01 1981-03; Folder 72:12
    - management records, 1981-04 1981-06; Folder 72:13
    - management records, 1981-07 1981-09; Folder 72:14
    - management records, 1981-10 1981-12; Folder 72:15
    - contract [A.R.E.; P.M.S. Products], 1982; Folder 72:16
  - Box 73
    - management records, 1982-01 1982-03; Folder 73:1
    - management records, 1982-04 1982-06; Folder 73:2
    - management records, 1982-07 1982-09; Folder 73:3
    - management records, 1982-10 1982-12; Folder 73:4
    - management records, 1983-01 1983-03; Folder 73:5
    - management records, 1983-04 1983-06; Folder 73:6
    - management records, 1983-07 1983-09; Folder 73:7
    - management records, 1983-10 1983-12; Folder 73:8
    - management records, 1984; Folder 73:9
    - staff minutes, 1984; Folder 73:10
    - management records, 1985; Folder 73:11
    - membership roster, 1985; Folder 73:12
    - staff minutes, 1985; Folder 73:13
    - testimonials, 1985 1987; Folder 73:14
    - management records, 1986; Folder 73:15
    - staff minutes, 1986; Folder 73:16
    - management records, 1987; Folder 73:17
    - staff minutes, 1987; Folder 73:18
    - staff minutes, 1988 1995; Folder 73:19
  - Box 74
    - management records, 1987; Folder 74:1
    - management records, 1988; Folder 74:2
    - management records, 1989; Folder 74:3
    - management records, 1990; Folder 74:4
    - staff minutes, 1990; Folder 74:5
    - management records, 1991; Folder 74:6
    - staff minutes, 1991; Folder 74:7
    - management records, 1992; Folder 74:8
    - staff minutes, 1992; Folder 74:9
    - management records, 1993; Folder 74:10
    - staff minutes, 1993; Folder 74:11
    - management records, 1994; Folder 74:12
    - staff minutes, 1994; Folder 74:13
    - management records, 1995; Folder 74:14
    - staff minutes, 1995; Folder 74:15
  - Box 75
    - management records, 1996; Folder 75:1
    - staff minutes, 1996; Folder 75:2
    - management records, 1997; Folder 75:3
    - management records, 1998; Folder 75:4
    - management records, 1999; Folder 75:5
    - staff minutes, 1997 1999; Folder 75:6
    - management records, 2000; Folder 75:7-75:9
    - staff minutes, 2000; Folder 75:10
    - student paper [volunteer service] Jessica Dambruch, 2004; Folder 75:11
- Prayer Services, 1932 2008
  - Box 76
    - class materials [A.R.E. Summer School class on Prayer Group readings], 1967; Folder 76:1; Turner, Albert E.
    - class materials [A.R.E. Summer School class on Prayer and Meditation: Techniques and Applications], 1961; Folder 76:2; Miller, Hannah; Fiutka, Joseph
    - correspondence [Glad Helpers Prayer Group], 1932 1979; Folder 76:3
    - minutes [A.R.E. Prayer Group], 1960-09-21 1961-07-26; Folder 76:4
    - minutes [Glad Helpers Prayer Group], 1969-12-10 1971-04-07; Folder 76:5
    - minutes [Glad Helpers Prayer Group], 1971-06-02 1972-07-12; Folder 76:6
    - minutes [Glad Helpers Prayer Group], 1972-07-26 1975-10-22; Folder 76:7
    - minutes [Joyous Healing Group], 1968-05-08 1969-10-15; Folder 76:8
    - minutes [Prayer for Healing Group], 1966-03-09 1968-05-01; Folder 76:9
    - notebook [Glad Helpers Prayer Group], 1957; Folder 76:10; Turner, Albert E.
    - notes [Dr. Alfred Price lectures at the A.R.E.], 1960; Folder 76:11; Turner, Albert E.
    - notes [group experiences during meditation and prayer], 1936 1969; Folder 76:12
    - notes [healing], 1935; Folder 76:13; Edmonds, Florence
    - publications [A.R.E. Prayer groups], 1933 1976; Folder 76:14-76:17
    - prayer commentaries, undated; Folder 76:18; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; LeNoir, Ruth
    - prayer leaflets {Glad Helpers], 1942 1977; Folder 76:19
    - prayer lists, 1934 1979; Folder 76:20
    - prayer lists, 1988 1991; Folder 76:21
    - prayer lists, 1992 2000; Folder 76:22
  - Box 77
    - prayer lists, 2001 2008; Folder 77:1-77:4
    - readings excerpts, 1932; Folder 77:5; Edmonds, Florence
    - register of applicants for prayers, 1933-01 1936-06-01; Folder 77:6
    - study group manual, 1932; Folder 77:7; Morrow, Frances Yelden King
  - Meredith Puryear files, 1968 2002
    - Box 78
      - book [A Search for God Book 1], Folder 78:1
      - affirmations, Folder 78:2
      - akashic records, Folder 78:3
      - angels, Folder 78:4
      - anger / stress management, Folder 78:5
      - A.R.E., Folder 78:6
      - A.R.E. catalogs / conference programs, Folder 78:7
      - A.R.E. Journal index, Folder 78:8
      - astral projections, Folder 78:9
      - astrology, Folder 78:10
      - bible, Folder 78:11-78:12
      - birthmarks, Folder 78:13
      - Blumenthal, Morton, Folder 78:14
      - castor oil packs, Folder 78:15
      - Cayce, Edgar, Folder 78:16
      - Cayce, Edgar: source of readings, Folder 78:17
      - channeled material, Folder 78:18
      - child development, Folder 78:19
      - Christ consciousness, Folder 78:20
      - Christmas, Folder 78:21
      - Covenant course, Folder 78:22
      - creation, Folder 78:23
      - death and dying, Folder 78:24
      - decision-making, Folder 78:25
      - diet, Folder 78:26
      - dreams, Folder 78:27
      - earth changes, Folder 78:28
      - Easter, Folder 78:29
      - Essenes, Folder 78:30
      - evolution, Folder 78:31
      - Exodus, Folder 78:32
      - extracts from the Edgar Cayce Readings, Folder 78:33
      - fear, Folder 78:34
      - forty-day prayer, Folder 78:35
      - fruits of the spirit, Folder 78:36
      - Garrett, Eileen, Folder 78:37
      - Glad Helpers, booklets, Folder 78:38
      - Glad Helpers, general, Folder 78:39
      - Glad Helpers, history, Folder 78:40
    - Box 79
      - Glad Helpers, ideals and purposes, Folder 79:1
      - Glad Helpers, relative to Search For God, Folder 79:2
      - glands, Folder 79:3
      - glossalalia, Folder 79:4
      - God, nature of, Folder 79:5
      - grace and karma, Folder 79:6
      - guides, gurus, and the Gospels, Folder 79:7
      - groups, Prayer Healing, Folder 79:8
      - healing, economic, Folder 79:9
      - healing, global, Folder 79:10
      - healing, panel discussion, Folder 79:11
      - healing, philosophy, Folder 79:12
      - healing, prayer, general, Folder 79:13
      - healing, prayer, laying on of hands, Folder 79:14
      - healing, prayer, mental, Folder 79:15
      - healing, prayer, physical, Folder 79:16
      - healing, prayer, spiritual, Folder 79:17
      - healing, rejuvenation, Folder 79:18
      - healing, scientific articles, Folder 79:19
      - Heard, Gerald, Folder 79:20
      - Hermes, Folder 79:21
      - home and marriage, Folder 79:22
      - hypnosis / meditation, Folder 79:23
      - ideal, Folder 79:24
      - I Ching, Folder 79:25
      - individuality / personality, Folder 79:26
      - infinite into the finite, Folder 79:27
      - Japanese publications, Folder 79:28
      - Jesus' picture, Folder 79:29
      - Jesus, second coming, Folder 79:30
      - Jesus, the pattern, Folder 79:31
    - Box 80
      - Jung, Carl, Folder 80:1
      - kindness, Folder 80:2
      - knowledge, Folder 80:3
      - kundalini influences, Folder 80:4
      - letters, samples, Folder 80:5
      - life seals / aura charts, Folder 80:6
      - lifestyle inventory, Folder 80:7
      - light, Folder 80:8
      - Lord's Prayer, Folder 80:9
      - love, Folder 80:10
      - loving indifference, Folder 80:11
      - mandalas, Folder 80:12
      - maps, Folder 80:13
      - medicine, preventative, Folder 80:14
      - meditation, attunement, Folder 80:15
      - meditation, books, Folder 80:16
      - meditation, confusion, Folder 80:17
      - meditation course, Folder 80:18
      - meditation, endocrine system, Folder 80:19
      - meditation, experiences, Folder 80:20
      - meditation, general, Folder 80:21
      - meditation, how to, Folder 80:22
      - meditation, Lord's Prayer, Folder 80:23
      - meditation, music, Folder 80:24
      - meditation, noon, Folder 80:25
      - meditation, protection, Folder 80:26
      - meditation, visualization, Folder 80:27
      - meditation room, angel, Folder 80:28
      - mental / spiritual readings, Folder 80:29
      - mind control, Silva method, Folder 80:30
      - mind, Folder 80:31
      - mind, the builder, Folder 80:32
      - miracles, Folder 80:33
      - miscellaneous, Folder 80:34
      - name, changing, Folder 80:35
      - nature of man, Folder 80:36
      - new age, Folder 80:37
      - numerology, Folder 80:38
      - oneness, Folder 80:39
      - open door, the, Folder 80:40
      - origin and destiny of man, Folder 80:41
      - Paul's journeys and ministry, Folder 80:42
      - poetry, Folder 80:43
      - possession, haunting, warnings, Folder 80:44
      - prayer, confession and attunement, Folder 80:45
      - prayer, death, Folder 80:46
      - prayer, direct and surround, Folder 80:47
      - prayer, effectiveness, Folder 80:48
      - prayer, forgiveness and thanksgiving, Folder 80:49
      - prayer, general, Folder 80:50
      - prayer group readings, Folder 80:51
    - Box 81
      - prayer, how to, Folder 81:1
      - prayer, intercessory, Folder 81:2
      - prayer, Lama Sing, Folder 81:3
      - prayer, name, use of, Folder 81:4
      - prayer, power, Folder 81:5
      - prayer, protection, Folder 81:6
      - prayer, scientific art, Folder 81:7
      - prayer, soul development, Folder 81:8
      - prayer services, how it works, Folder 81:9
      - prayer services, development, Folder 81:10
      - prayers, Folder 81:11
      - psalms, Folder 81:12
      - psychic development, Folder 81:13
      - psychotherapeutics, Folder 81:14
      - religions of the world, Folder 81:15
      - remedies, physical, Folder 81:16
      - revelation, Folder 81:17